

## CONTACT

+358 0449239180

https://www.linkedin.com/in/th araka-ranathunga-58ba52205/

https://github.com/TharakaRana thunga

💡 Kivikatu 5 B 51, 15700, Lahti

## **SKILLS**

Team Player

**Public Relations** 

Time Management

Leadership

**Effective Communication** 

Critical Thinking

## **DIGITAL SKILLS**

Microsoft Office HTML & Java Script Python

# LANGUAGE SKILLS

Sinhala (Mother tongue)

**English (Fluent)** 

Chinese (Good)

Japanese (Good)

Finnish (Basic)

TKT CLILL - Band 4

PTE - 78

HSK Level 4

JLPT Level 3

### CERTIFICATES

Hygiene Passport

# THARAKA RANATHUNGA

#### **PROFILE**

I am a highly motivated professional with a proven track, a strong team player who thrives on collaboration, and a committed learner who takes up challenges. I am also a hard worker who always tries to complete the responsibilities taking the optimum output in providing the industry with the best production with knowledge, expertise and research.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### CLEANER (PART-TIME) INHOUSE PARTNERS OY, LAHTI

01/11/2024 - Present Lahti

Cleaning supermarket premises

#### ADVERTISEMENT DISTRIBUTOR (PART-TIME) SSM OY

28/08/2024 - Present

Lahti Sorting and delivering advertisements

#### **LECTURER - SABARAGAMUWA UNIVERSITY OF SRI LANKA**

03/05/2020 - 30/06/2024 Belihuloya, Sri Lanka

- Teaching Mandarin Chinese and Japanese to undergraduates
- Curriculum designing, assessing and evaluating students' works
- Organizing and conducting workshops, field tours, conferences and examinations
- Taking minutes of meetings, recording and reporting

## **INSTRUCTOR - SRI LANKA INTERNATIONAL BUDDHIST ACADEMY**

15/01/2018 - 30/04/2020 Colombo, Sri Lanka

- Designing course content
- Teaching Chinese and English language to undergraduates and diploma students, assessing and evaluating students' works
- Conducting meetings, workshops and events

#### **EDUCATION**

BACHELOR OF ENGINEERING IN INDUSTRIAL INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY-LAB UNIVERSITY OF APPLIED SCIENCES, LAHTI, FINLAND

15/08/2024 - PRESENT

MASTER OF ARTS IN LINGUISTICS - UNIVERSITY OF KELANIYA, SRI LANKA 19/04/2019-01/05/2023

BACHELOR OF ARTS - SABARAGAMUWA UNIVERSITY OF SRI LANKA 16/07/2013 - 10/11/2017

CERTIFICATE IN COMPUTER SCIENCE - NATIONAL INSTITUTE OF BUSINESS MNAGEMENT, SRI LANKA

CONTENT AND LANGUAGE INTEGRATED LEARNING - AUSTRALIAN COLLEGE OF BUSINESS AND TECHNOLOGY

DIPLOMA IN AIRLINE TICKETING - INTERNATIONAL AIRLINE TICKETING ACADEMY, SRI LANKA